Satoru
Is that Satoru?
No, it's not.
Who is that?
Ninguém ta conhece
Bet you're watching it, boss 고맙다
Seelf
Sup생ado
Errame
Melo
Miteillazim Boys
Oh
I'm Michael Sohn!
Whoa!
Yeah!
You're up.
Good morning.
Why'd you get up so early?
Isn't it obvious? I'm making breakfast.
You are heading off to school early again, aren't you?
Yeah.
It looks good.
Slow down, kiddo. You'll make yourself sick.
Can I ask you something, Satoru?
Mm-hmm.
Who are you meeting this early in the morning?
Can't tell.
You're not doing anything bad, are you?
Of course not.
Okay, then.
See you later, Mom.
Hold it.
Take this, too.
It's a little something extra.
You know, if you get hungry before lunch.
Right.
Thanks a bunch, Mom.
It's me. Good morning.
Good morning, Satoru.
I brought you some breakfast.
Thanks, but did you eat anything yet?
Yep.
This is all yours.
Wow.
It looks yummy.
How are you doing?
You must be bored.
Too bad this place doesn't have a TV.
It's me. Good morning.
Good morning, Satoru.
I brought you some breakfast.
Thanks, but did you eat anything yet?
Yep, this is all yours.
Wow, it looks yummy.
How are you doing?
You must be bored.
Too bad this place doesn't have a TV.
It's okay.
I'm not as bored as you think.
Hiromi brought a ton of books yesterday.
That's good.
Think you can hold out for another couple days?
Mm-hmm.
That was so good.
See you later.
Mm-hmm.
Crap.
School's about to start at Izumi Elementary.
I was at the bus for too long.
This grad ceremony's gonna suck.
I have to give the speech.
Please, you'll be great.
You're better at giving speeches than me, Aya.
Not even, Saki.
It'll be fine.
You'll see.
Just have a little courage.
I guess Kaio's absent, again.
You're her friend.
Do you know what's up with her?
No.
No one was home when I went by there.
Where is she?
I mean, if she was sick, we would've heard.
Yeah.
But there's been no word yet from her mom, anyway.
Come on, I'm sure she'll show up sooner or later like she always does.
So how about we get started?
Really?
No one was there this morning either, huh?
Are you worried?
Mm-hmm.
You don't look like you're all that worried.
I'm just trying to stay calm.
Like you always say, panicking never helps anyone.
You're right.
I tried calling Kaio's yesterday and today, but there's no answer.
Also, I tried calling the place where her mother works.
They told me she hasn't been in.
Well then, call the CPS people or the police!
The police, huh?
I don't know.
I'd hate to open a can of worms.
For someone else, that is.
I called CPS yesterday, though.
They'll visit her house today.
And I'm going to meet them.
I'm pretty sure if we all show up there, we'll get to the bottom of things.
It's like I always say in class, where there's a will, there's a way.
You're the best!
Miss Inazuki, we're with Child Protective Services.
Is she even home?
Well, all the lights are on, so someone has to be.
Why don't we have a look around the back?
Miss Inazuki, are you home?
Kaio?
I'm coming in.
What?
You can't just walk in.
Don't worry.
If anyone complains, I'll take the blame.
The girl's been missing for three days now.
It's worth a shot.
The stove and the lights are on.
There's a half-eaten dinner on the coffee table.
I don't see Kaio's coat anywhere.
By the looks of it, her mom was just here a minute ago.
She left in a hurry.
I bet she saw us pull up.
By the time we got to the door, she was out the back.
Damn it.
I was hoping we could take custody of the girl tonight.
Look, her mother can't stay out in this cold all night.
As soon as we leave, I'm sure she'll come back.
We can try again tomorrow morning.
I'm worried about Kaio's safety, though.
We could get the police to put an APB out on the mom.
Uh-uh.
I have a feeling Kaio's safe.
In fact, I'm positive she is.
Okay, we'll take your word for it.
We'll leave for now.
Give the mother a chance to calm down.
Mr. Yashiro and Child Protective Services were just at your house.
They were looking for your mom, but she wasn't there.
By tomorrow, all of this might be over.
Kaio, they said they'd take you away from her.
That's okay.
I'd be way happier without her.
We knew if they took her away from her mom,
they'd be taking her away from us, too.
It'll be hard to go, but I'll be fine.
Whenever I think of you guys, I'll remember all the fun we had.
Satoru, I know it's a little late, but...
I finished your birthday present.
Here you go.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
Promise.
Thank you.
It feels like...
I don't know.
Like I've been waiting for this forever.
It doesn't take much to make you tear up, huh?
Wait, what?
Oh, hey, Satoru.
Can you spend the night?
That's totally gutsy!
Dorks.
Last night, someone came in while I was sleeping.
He just walked in.
I don't think he knew I was here.
But it scared me.
Maybe it was a security guard or a janitor.
It could have been anyone.
Some pervy kid stashing his porn.
Who knows?
It was a grown-up.
Whoever it was was mad.
He kicked that box super hard.
Let's open it.
I hope it's nothing worse than porn.
What's that for?
I knew.
I knew right away what all that stuff was for.
Then it hit me.
This old bus we were in was out behind Izumi Elementary.
The school where Aya Nakanishi, the killer's next victim, went.
We hadn't escaped the loop of kidnappings and murders yet.
March the 2nd.
Sometime after 10 that night, Kaio disappeared from the shed behind her house.
Tracks found around the shed were from a pair of rubber boots.
They matched a pair Yuki owned.
The killer put Kaio in a walk-in freezer and sprayed water on her to make her freeze to death faster.
Then, the killer took her body back to the shed before dawn.
We can't stay here.
This bus is at the center of the killer's routine.
It's not safe here.
No.
No, it's not.
Our plan was to have someone find Kaio here.
But now, after seeing this crap, we better move her.
Mm-hmm.
We don't want some creep to find her.
Well, I hope you have a plan B.
I do.
Awesome.
Okay.
Let's clear out.
Remember what that footprint looks like.
What's all that black stuff?
Charcoal on a stove.
Was the killer going to use this to...
No!
Satoru.
Flipping out isn't going to help.
Yeah, you're right.
I gotta keep a clear head.
All right.
Let's get going.
It was such a cool hideout.
Right.
But not of some weirdos using it, too.
Yeah.
However we do it,
we need to make damn sure Kaio stays out of the killer's range.
But now, with Child Protective Services on the case,
the future has to change.
It's got to.
Wait.
This is plan B?
Mm-hmm.
Simple, huh?
There's just one last hurdle.
It would have saved us a lot of hassle if you thought of...
I'm home.
It's about time.
Um...
Uh...
Hello.
All right.
What's going on?
I'm helping a friend in trouble.
That's what.
Way to go, guys.
Good job.
I was hoping you'd be okay with this.
For a sec, I thought you were gonna kick my butt.
I did it again.
Now, why on earth would you think that?
This is exactly what friends are for.
What you cooking?
I could smell it when I came in.
Oh, nothing much.
Just a big fat pot of curry is all.
I had a feeling you'd be bringing over a couple of friends tonight.
My mom can read me like a book.
Don't just stand there.
Pull up a chair.
Would you like some curry?
Yes, please.
It smells yummy.
It's good I brought everyone, because you made a ton.
If you didn't, you'd be eating curry for the rest of the month.
Um, Miss Fujinuma?
I brought this back.
It was delicious.
Well, my job's done for the night.
Have fun washing the dishes, kiddo.
Thanks, Mom.
See you later.
Bye-bye.
Later, guys.
Mr. Yashiro, this is Satoru Fujinuma's mom.
Actually, I do.
Satoru just brought Kayo back to my place, and she's okay.
Ah, what a relief.
That's good to hear.
I knew they were in this together.
Yeah, it's great, but what happens to her now?
Will she be put in foster care?
Good question.
You know, I've been thinking about it, and I might have an idea.
No, we tried to, but her mother wasn't home.
Maybe you can help, but only if you don't mind.
Hey, Kayo, you want to spend the night?
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
I'm sorry to call so late.
I'm Gaku Yashiro, a teacher at Mikoto Elementary.
I need to talk to you about Kayo.
He's called Wonder Guy.
Isn't he cool?
Okay, guys, bath time.
Who wants to go first?
I'll go after you.
You know what?
How about we go together?
Hey, Kayo, come here and let me wash your hair.
Um, no thank you.
I can do it.
It's okay.
I want to.
How are we doing, miss?
Are we feeling fabulous yet?
And now it's time for...
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle.
And more tickles.
And more, and more.
Hello, you're 29.
We better dry your hair or you're going to catch a cold.
Um, you guys like to have a good bath?
Yeah.
It was lots of fun.
That's good.
Wait, those are your pajamas?
Now they are.
I bought them for her.
Witch.
These are fresh and ready to go.
They're super soft.
Thank you.
Have you done this before?
You gotta pull your end tight.
This totally reminds me.
The class took a trip to Hakodate
and the view from the top of the mountain was rad.
What?
You've never been to Hakodate.
Crap.
Oh, must have been a photo I saw.
Okay.
You ready for lights out?
Yes.
Oh, it's so funny.
My house doesn't have a night light.
Oh, yeah?
I can turn it off if you want.
Uh-uh.
It's fine like this.
Why don't we leave it on tonight?
You got it.
Thanks, Satoru.
Night, guys.
Night, Mom.
I'm not in the way here, am I?
Yep.
No, of course not.
There I go again.
Stop.
What'd you do that for?
Oops.
I meant to do this.
Ow.
And this.
Stop it.
Never.
You're an idiot.
Good morning.
Morning.
You awake?
If you are, shake a leg.
Breakfast is going to get cold.
Okay.
I'm starving.
Wait.
No curry?
That's your dinner.
For the next month.
What?
There can't be that much left.
You'll just have to invite everyone over again.
Bye-bye.
Oh.
Missou –
Mm-hmm.
Goddamn little!
Mom?
Kaio! You little shit! Where the hell have you been?
I'll shoot!
I should have known.
Kunaishivi mo…yorokobi mo…
Subbete…
Bona inaru p eating Canada
Yasaishiku naaru…
ことだと figurabisa no subete…
Undo na ni naru…
protecting
See you next time.
君が笑うこの世界の歌 乗り戻すよ